Diana Davies Papers, 1960s-1996 (ongoing)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- The Railroads, Hoboes and Subways
  - Hoboes
    - Hoboes, and the World of Freight Hoppers Unlimited: photos, letters, info, drawings (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - The Railroads
    - Trains in Western Mass, 1992. Cabooses on siding. "Scabs Rule", "Save the Railroads - STRR" - graffiti (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Tracks with snow. Northampton, Mass, 1992. Weeds near tracks (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Depot and tracks, 1994. Northampton, Mass. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - R.R. Station and tracks. Northampton, Mass, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Train depot, Belfast and Moosehead (a.k.a. RR, Maine, 1993 - accordian player in station (B and ML RR) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - B and ML RR, Maine, 1991. Yard and caboose (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Waldo Station, 1992. B and ML RR, Maine (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Belfast Station, B and ML RR, 1992, Maine (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - B and ML RR train yard and equipment (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - B and ML RR train yard, 1993. Round house, cabooses, cars, parts (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - B and ML RR, color slides. Tracks, station. Trains and interiors, passengers (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Penn Central Tracks, 1966. NYC - color slides (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - South Station, Boston, 1993. Dancing and band in station, passengers, commuters (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Boston "T" subway, 1992. "Red Line" kids playing on floor (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Subway series, NYC 1965-1970 - a whole lotta underground stuff (most were published) (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - NYC from "The El" - elevated subway line, early 1960s (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Western Mass Women and Community Groups
  - Lesbian-Gay Pride march, Northampton, Mass. (includes Paula Gottlieb, Molly Babize, Trina Hope, Alice Barrett, Laura Kaye, Susan Levine), 1983 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Interfaith pilgrimage on the route of the third passage, 1998, Northampton support rally - includes Athena Stylos, artist and Mary Hynes, weaver (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Mary Hynes, artist and craftswoman and social justice activist, 1996. Wendell, Mass (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Paula Gottlieb art show at Lunaria Books, late 1980s. Northampton, Mass (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Lunaria Bookstore, 1990. Includes - co-founder Madeline Zadik; guests - Crystal Chemris, Kady and Madeline's dog (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Artist-activist Laura Kaye and visitors at her home in Wendell, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - "Dor" - Dorthee, a craftswoman, activist, 1983. Leverett, Mass. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Mary Hynes, Dor, Kady, 1989 - playing marbles, planting trees. Wendell (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - JoAnn Aalfs, community activist, 1991, Northampton (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Activist Kathryn Wetzel, early 1980s, at her tag sale, Northampton (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Monster, org.
    - Flyers, info from Monster. Western Mass Anarcha - feminist group. Late 1990s (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Revolutionary Anarchist Youth (RAY)
    - Photos, papers, flyers, publications. Includes - photos of Caitlin Kiely and Nicole Byer with banner, etc. on living wage day, Northampton (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - RAY activists/organizers. Includes - Ruby Bottlerocket, Morgan Kennedy, Nicole Byer, Dada Welch, Northampton, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - RAY organizers. Includes - Heidi Reijm, Steve Theberge, Ben Tyler, Dana Welch, Jess Klatzker, Cybèle Collins, Cat Bohannon, Jeff (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Info and flyers (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Info and flyers (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Zines, published by RAY (D. Davies, contributor) (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Valley Arts and Music Alliance (VAMA) and Flywheel
    - Valley Arts and Music Alliance (VAMA) and Flywheel Arts Space Collectively organized and run community gallery, infoshop, performance space, café. Photos, papers and designs by Diana Jo, for Flywheel-VAMA, 1998 - (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Youth Rights
      - The Youth Summit at Hampshire College, 1997. Youth Rights conference - U.S. and international representation and participation in workshops and events by social justice and youth rights activists (includes Marta, organizer) (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - The Youth Summit info, publications and flyers (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Women's Zines and Publications
  - Ella: a journal of women in music, Western Mass, 1996-1997 (DJD contributor) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Earth Rites - a Zine/journal edited by Sherry Mestel, 1978 and 1980 (DJD contributor) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Riot Grrrl - Zines and posters, early 1990s (DJD and local contributors) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Women's Zines, miscellaneous, includes - Thirteen Zine, Death and Tortillas, Sister Suberter, Spectacular Times, Gun Moll, Feminist Action, Hey Angel, Boingo, Buffy Meets Fire Kitten, No Longer Silent, Discombobulated Triagathoid, Madwoman, Shut up and Listen, Lucky Starr (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Street Kids Project, Maine, 1993
  - The Street Kids Book: "Art Underground and Beyond…" These 6 folders contain material from a large notebook which documented the struggle(s) of street kids fighting a curfew act against kids under 18 years old. Kids organized, held meetings, put out flyers and petitions, got the ACLU to help, put on a huge multi-media art show. This is also a story of their working together, and tells and shows us about the art show. It is a story of community and organizing. It is a story of human rights (Box 32, Folder 1-6)
  - Sketchbook: "Draw or write in here, please…" sketchbook from the kids' art show (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Story-article: "Survive the Night - A Curfew Story" by Diana Davies - article (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Small photos of street kids project (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
  - Clippings, info, letters, published material, addresses, art show organizing material (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Street kids, supporters
    - Street kids' supporter, artist Ollie Nuse (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Stone soup kitchen a friend and food have for the street folk (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Backstage at the gallery - supporters and the art show (includes artists Heather Curtis and A.J. Dutch) (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Supporters Claire, Jocey, and Felicia and their 2nd-hand store (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Supporters of Youth Rights at Felicia and Leticia's house (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - The Curfew
    - Signs, on buildings, calling for fight against curfew (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Kids on bicycles protest the curfew (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Street kids' supporters and the chief of police, Belfast, Maine (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Street kids and supporters playing hacky-sack and music in the streets (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Street kids and supporters playing music, talking, etc (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Street kids - "Charley" and supporters (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - All-ages Space
    - A "Chem-free", all ages club in Portland, kids welcome (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Youth Rights supporters (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Street kids and supporters truck (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Extra "8x10" prints (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Mexico, Cuba, Portugal, Spain, late 1960s, early 1970s and 1990s
  - Mexico - Radical politics
    - Support for EZLN and radical social justice in Chiapa, Mexico. - Demonstration in Northampton, Mass - by five colleges (Includes Nosotras, Smith College Latina group) 1998 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Zapatista - EZLN representative Cecelia Rodriguez speaks at Smith College, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Elena Poniatowska, radical Mexican historian, journalist, writer speaks and reads at Mt. Holyoke College, 1998 and copies of "Tlatelolco" painting done for E. Poniatowska - by Diana Davies, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Mexico city - color slides, 1968 - miscellaneous street scenes (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Cuba
    - Fidel Castro, 1968 - at 2 events - rally and arts reception. Havana, Cuba (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Dancers at community center, near Havana (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Havana, 1968. Miscellaneous street scenes and street festival - celebration (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Havana, 1968. Color slides - street scenes, mental institution with women inmates, Havana greenbelt, street rally, signs (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Portugal
    - Miscellaneous color slides, Lisbon 1969 and 1970. Women working and going to public market, women working in street, "street urchins" street scene (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Public arts festival, 1969, Lisbon - folk arts performances and audience (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Spain
    - Madrid, Spain-1969, street scenes (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Israel - Palestine (and related material from NYC)
  - Golda Meir in Jerusalem, Tel Aviv, and NYC, 1967 and 1970 (color and b&w ) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Israel - Palestine. Miscellaneous 1969 and 1970, Arab and Israeli culture and political and social scenes. Old city, Jerusalem, Tel Aviv. Israeli army, craftspeople, market scenes, sports event, wailing wall, U.N. vehicles (includes Moshe Dayan, Golda Meir, Yigal Allon) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Israel/Palestine 1970. Jerusalem, Kidron Valley, Jericho (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Journal excerpts and on-the-road flashbacks and published material (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Color slides, 1969 and 1970. Arab and Israeli culture (mostly Jerusalem and old city) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Color slides - Israeli army and military. Irrigated land/agricultural projects, Landscapes, Hebrew Univ., Archaeological digs, Jaffa Arts and Crafts, sports (and - pro-Israeli demo in NYC during "6-day war" 1967). Kibbutzim (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Animals - Creatures (and more "best-friends")
  - Max the cat, in window, 1969. Lower East side, NYC (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Gertrude (dog), Max (cat) and visiting small cat, Lower East side, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Gertrude (dog), George (dog), Max (cat), 1973. NY State (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Gertrude (dog), Max (cat), Roxbury, Mass, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Billie Jean cat woman and the other barn cats. 1974, NY State (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Billie Jean and Max (cats), 1976. NY State (close-ups) ("The Cat Under the Stool") (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Billie Jean (cat), Gertrude (dog), 1975. Catskill Mtns., NY State (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Billie Jean (cat), George (dog), Max (cat) and the basket house. 1976, NY State (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Max (big cat) and Hawk and Richard (small cats) and Kady. NY State, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Barnyard - farm cats at birdfeeders. Forestburgh (Catskill Mtns.) NY State, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - "Tillie" the dog and "Millie" (the 1966 Ford Mustang) on the road, 1977. And Tillie and the house (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Gertrude (dog) in "The Blizzard of '78" Boston, Mass, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Billie Jean cat woman and the piano ("The Cat on the Piano" 1979, Jamacia Plain, Mass. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Jessie (dog) - Pat Styer's dog, 1980, Northampton, Mass (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Gertrude (dog), Jesse (dog), 1982, Woodstock, NY (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - The two singing (howling?) dogs. Coastal Maine, 1992. In parking lot, in car (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - The gargoyle dogs at the Zertgeist Gargoyle Shop. 1993, Portland, Maine (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - "Animals on the Job" - "Bum" - the garage dog. 1966 and 1967, NY State (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - "The Ghost Cat" in storefront window. Market St., Northampton, Mass.,1982 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - "Sammy" - the orange cat. Northampton, Mass 1995 (a jazz band's cat) (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Alley cats who live behind "Joe's Café" (pizza joint) 1993. Northampton, Mass (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Alley cats, Amherst, Mass.,1985 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Old dog on porch, rural slum neighborhood. Costal Maine, 1992 (and weeds and textures) (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - "Harlequin" - the two-tone dog. Northampton, Mass.,1995 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - 2 "orange" dogs on Main St. Northampton, Mass 1994 (and flowers and crocuses) (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - "Patchwork" dog and shadow on Main St. Northampton, Mass 1995 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - "Apple" the cat (Barbara Deming's cat friend) 1973, NY State (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Cat in second story window. Coastal Maine, Rte. 1, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Cats and dogs. Prints from color slides in this file, miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Cats and dogs - color slides, miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Bird next and eggs (print and color slide) 1966. NY State (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Assorted creatures - color slides. Frogs, possums, farm animals, camel, ducks, lizards, birds, etc (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - "Cow Friendship" (2 cows) - series. Western Mass, 1987 (the cow series) (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Longhorned cows. Rural Maine (the cow series), 1991 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Molly the woodchuck and her children, Coastal Maine, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - The possum in the shed. 1974 (possum squats in storage shed) Catskill Mtns., NY State (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - The grasshopper in the thistle. Catskill Mtns., 1987 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Snake on rocks, flowers, moths, weeds, garden (includes Kady and Marian Wagner) 1987. Catskill Mtns (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Huge snake (pit viper) 1984. Catskill Mtns., NY State (in back of Kady's house) (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Spider webs. Catskill Mtns. Forestburgh, NY State, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - The red-headed bird, Western Mass, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Bird tracks, Boston, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Flying bird viewed through picket fence and opera house. Coastal Maine and "Blizzard of '78", Boston, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Ducks in a pond. 1990 off Rte. 202, New Hampshire (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - The three geese -or- ducks. 1986. Catskill Mtns., NY State (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - The white and speckled horse in the dirty-white barn. 1994. Northampton, Mass fairgrounds (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Horse - in pasture and dog, "Dali" - in record store. Off rte. 1, Coastal Maine, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Raccoon, Woodstock, NY-Catskill Mtns., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Farmyard, NY State. Catskill Mtns., early 1960s - Mule, chickens, goat (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Cats and dogs watch deer through window. 1976, Catskill Mtns., Forestburgh, NY (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - The deer series - snowscapes and deer-Catskill Mtns., 1986. NY State (color) (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - The deer series - grazing spring., 1974 (b&w ) (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - The deer series - miscellaneous color slides and prints. 1970s, Catskill Mtns., NY State (Box 35, Folder 53)
- Nature and Farms
  - Trees, miscellaneous - prints from slides in this file box (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Trees - tree bark, roots, leaves, plants, textures, miscellaneous color slides (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Trees - tree bark, roots, plants, textures, miscellaneous color slides (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Trees, plants, textures, color internegs from slides in this box (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Tree roots and stream, 1990. Ashfield, Mass. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - "Lie on your back in the grass and take a picture of a tree…" (an assignment to myself) 1972. Catskill Mtns., NY State (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Trees and vines. Trees and sunset, 1983. Catskill Mtns., NY State (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Tree - "Dogwood" and plants (Jack in the Pulpit) 1984, NY State (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Olive trees and bark. Gethsemane Garden Jerusalem, 1969 or 1970 (b&w and color) (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Ice breaking-up in river. Tree stump and roots - "The Forest Wall" 1990 Coastal Maine (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Textures, plants, shoots, twiggy-things, rocks, bricks. 1995 Hadley, Mass (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Textures - weeds, wood, rocks, ice. Coastal Maine 1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Flowers, weeds, wood, stream. Western Mass, 1986 and textures (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Textures - pond, rocks, weeds and trailers!!! New Hampshire - off Rte. 202, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Rocks, textures. Near Beach, Newport, RI, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - The ice storm. March 1995, Northampton, Mass. (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - "The Beach Rubble Series" Provincetown, Cape Cod, Mass.,1980s (from a traveling exhibit and notebook) (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Mushrooms - toadstools, NY State, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Flowers
    - "Still-life" - daffodils and plant. Daffodils in the Blue Garden, 1991 (the blue-tone print experiment) (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Wildflowers and berries, 1987. Catskill Mtns., NY State (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Sunflower, tree bark and fungus. Catskill Mtns., NY State, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Flowers on "The Bridge of Flowers" Shelburne Falls, Mass.,1995 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Flowers, miscellaneous prints from slides in this file box (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Flowers, miscellaneous color slides (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Flowers, miscellaneous color slides (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Western Mass
    - Green tomatoes. Western Mass farms, wildflowers, weeds, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Tomatoes, ripe. Western Mass farms. Summer squash, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Old cucumber-picking vehicle, farmlands, surreal tress. Greenfield, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Cummington Fair, Aug. 1994. Rural farmlife, agriculture, animals, theatre, etc. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Old sled, 1992. Northampton, Western Mass (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Farmland, Green river, ducks, old car. Rte. 2, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Skies, milkweed pods, weeds, vines, Western Mass 1986 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Skies, sunflowers, veggies, rocks, chimpmunk, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Icicles on bush, 1992. Greenfield (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Pat's purple crocuses, 1995, Northampton (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Horizontal icicles, 1981, Northampton (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Trees and textures (miscellaneous), 1987. Northampton (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Nature-in-the-alleys. 1992, Northampton (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Fields and flowers - sticks and stones - Bay Rd. to So. Hadley - on foot. 1987 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Weeds, sunflowers, seed pods, tree stumps and textures. Near Turners Falls and Wendell, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Streambed, roses, weeds. Walking along Rte. 116, Ashfield 1986 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Double-rainbow near Greenfield, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Sweet gum tree seed pods, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Tree branches and vines, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Rte. 116, landscapes (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - "October Roses" roses growing outdoors in Oct. 1986. Northampton (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Streambed, rocks. Off Rte. 9, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Winter, 1987, Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - New York State
    - Farmscapes - slides from Catskill Mtn. Farms, 1970s (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Old apple orchard and stained glass, 1970s. Forestburgh, NY - print from slide in this box (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Apples, dragonflies, pond plants, thistles, 1984. Forestburgh, NY (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Winter at Squirrels Corners, 1986 (includes Kady) (series) color (Forestburgh, NY) (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Winter at Squirrels Corners - series, cont. (1986) color (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Winter at Squirrels Corners - series, cont. (1986) color (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Country winter, 1973. Squirrels Corners. Forestburgh, NY (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Old shale (road rock) crushing machine, 1973. Forestburgh (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Rural color - barns, sleds, tress - Kady with her dog (George). Old man Arthur and the house he was born in, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Trees, stumps, laurel, clover, new trees, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Ice storm, Squirrels Corners, 1970s. Forestburgh (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Vermont
    - North on Rtes. 5 and 91, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Coast - Maine
    - Gulf of Maine by boat, 1987. Beach plums, seagull in flight (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Wildflowers off Rte. 1. Coastal, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Old farm hay machine and fall leaves. Coast, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Pier, rocks, rowboats. Coast off Rte. 1-1989 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Weeds, trees, harbor, "Blue Goose Café", Coastal, Rtes. 1 and 3 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Weeds, seed pods and such, Coastal. 1987 off Rte. 15 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Country road, winter off Rte. 1. Harbor, old house, textures, tress, farmland (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Bar Harbor: shoreline water, firs. land - seascapes 1988 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Bar Harbor: shoreline, land-seascapes, seagulls, dinghy, harbor 1987 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Bar Harbor: shoreline, tress, tree roots, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Bar Harbor: Acadia National Park - color slides, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Coast, off rte. 1 Driftwood, rocks, weeds, woodchuck (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Belfast Harbor off rte. 1, 1988. Beach Plum, rosehips, wharf boats (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Weeds, fences, barbedwire, tree, harbor scenes, "Island Girl" boat, coast off rte. 1, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Winter (1987-88) N.E., rte. 1 Coast, Trailers!, coves, trees, dog in pickup truck, rural scenes (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Winter (1987-88) NE coastal, rte. 1. Snowdrifts, leaves, ice on river, etc. (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Winter (1987-88) NE coastal, rte. 1. Harbor scenes, textures (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Apples orchard, leaves on ground, bare branches, old shed (part 1) (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - "Renovated" old shed (part 2) summer, early fall 1988. Rte 187, off rte 1 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Flotsam and jetsam, crab, boatyard, houses, wharf, lobster pots, etc., rocks, seaweed. Stonington, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Laundry line, lobster pots, harbor, lobster shack, Stonington 1976 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Boats, seaweed, lobsterpots, boatyard, harbor, seagull on toy boat. 1976-1977 Stonington and Burnt Cove (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Harbor scenes, miscellaneous coastal. Rte 15, various dates (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Snowperson and barn. Maine central train, weeds. 1987 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Camden, Lincolnville Beach-Harbor scenes, beach, vines, seed pods, snow, 1987. Coastal, rte. 1 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Textures, vines, pods, feather, fence, leaf. Camden, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Coastal scenes, cattails, bushes, "Red's Eats" café, pond. Fall colors, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - End winter - begin spring. 1989. Rte. 1 coast, textures, rocks, harbor (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Upper Maine coast, rtes. 1 and 15. After "a small hurricane," 1989. Stuff washed up on beaches (includes Kady, exploring debris) (Box 38, Folder 29)
- The Miscellany Box
  - Work
    - People in the thick of the job - workplace miscellaneous various dates/locations (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Fishing industry, Cape Cod (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Places, Sight
    - South Street Seaport, NY City, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - NY City street scenes (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - NY Harbor from Staten Island ferry and 5 cent fare booths for ferry, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - East river from FDR Drive (and harbor) 1966 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Artwork and Design by Diana Jo Davies
  - "How to…" notebook -designs and info- (and tips or suggestions) and a book-in-progress (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Burnett Gallery sow, 2000. "The Portrait Show" at Jones Library, Amherst. Info, designs, published material (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Silkscreened patches (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Shows/workshops organized or curated by DJD (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Colrain war tax resistance, 1993. Jailed protesters in the Franklin County Courthouse. Greenfield, Mass. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Designs for Food Not Bombs organization, 1990s (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Portraits and poster and card designs - "Radical Women" series - (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Work done for AFSC - American Friends Service Committee (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Posters and illustrations - radical social justice themes and logos (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Illustrations and designs "Women" - varied portraits (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Pool-hall women. Drawings of girls who play the game (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - "Women and Music" - illustrations and designs (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous themes and portraits - designs and drawings (Box 40, Folder 13)